{
   "response_code":0,
   "results":[
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Cartoon%20%26%20Animations",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"What%20town%20was%20%22Springfield%22%20from%20%22The%20Simpsons%22%20originally%20named%20after%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Springfield%2C%20Oregon",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Springfield%2C%20Missouri",
            "Springfield%2C%20Illinois",
            "Springfield%2C%20Massachusetts"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"Which%20of%20these%20characters%20in%20%22Undertale%22%20can%20the%20player%20NOT%20go%20on%20a%20date%20with%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Toriel",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Papyrus",
            "Undyne",
            "Alphys"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Science%20%26%20Nature",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"What%20is%20isobutylphenylpropanoic%20acid%20more%20commonly%20known%20as%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Ibuprofen",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Morphine",
            "Ketamine",
            "Aspirin"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Science%20%26%20Nature",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"Which%20of%20these%20chemical%20compounds%20is%20NOT%20found%20in%20gastric%20acid%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Sulfuric%20acid",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Hydrochloric%20acid",
            "Potassium%20chloride",
            "Sodium%20chloride"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Japanese%20Anime%20%26%20Manga",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"In%20%22Highschool%20of%20the%20Dead%22%2C%20where%20did%20Komuro%20and%20Saeko%20establish%20to%20meet%20after%20the%20bus%20explosion%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Eastern%20Police%20Station",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "The%20Center%20Mall",
            "Komuro%27s%20House",
            "On%20The%20Main%20Bridge"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"General%20Knowledge",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"How%20long%20did%20it%20take%20the%20motorized%20window%20washers%20of%20the%20original%20World%20Trade%20Center%20to%20clean%20the%20entire%20exterior%20of%20the%20building%3F",
         "correct_answer":"1%20Month",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "3%20Weeks",
            "1%20Week",
            "2%20Months"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"The%20key%20of%20sharps%20does%20the%20key%20of%20G%23%20minor%20contain%3F",
         "correct_answer":"5",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "3",
            "7",
            "0"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"Who%20played%20the%20sun%20baby%20in%20the%20original%20run%20of%20Teletubbies%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Jessica%20Smith",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Pui%20Fan%20Lee",
            "Sue%20Monroe",
            "Lisa%20Brockwell"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Geography",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"What%20city%20is%20known%20as%20the%20Rose%20Capital%20of%20the%20World%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Tyler%2C%20Texas",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "San%20Diego%2C%20California",
            "Miami%2C%20Florida",
            "Anaheim%2C%20California"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Vehicles",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"In%202014%2C%20over%206%20million%20General%20Motors%20vehicles%20were%20recalled%20due%20to%20what%20critical%20flaw%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Faulty%20ignition%20switch",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Malfunctioning%20gas%20pedal",
            "Breaking%20fuel%20lines",
            "Faulty%20brake%20pads"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"Which%20game%20in%20the%20%22Monster%20Hunter%22%20series%20introduced%20the%20monster%20%22Gobul%22%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Monster%20Hunter%20Tri",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Monster%20Hunter%20Freedom%20Unite",
            "Monster%20Hunter%20Frontier",
            "Monster%20Hunter%20Generations"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"History",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20German%20offensive%20operation%20in%20October%201941%20to%20take%20Moscow%20before%20winter%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Operation%20Typhoon",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Operation%20Sunflower",
            "Operation%20Barbarossa",
            "Case%20Blue"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"Electronic%20artists%20Boys%20Noize%20and%20Skrillex%20have%20collaborated%20and%20released%20tracks%20under%20what%20name%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Dog%20Blood",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Jack%20%C3%9C",
            "What%20So%20Not",
            "Noisia"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Music",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"What%20was%20the%20name%20of%20the%20rock%20band%20that%20Nobuo%20Uematsu%20formed%20that%20played%20songs%20from%20various%20Final%20Fantasy%20games%3F",
         "correct_answer":"The%20Black%20Mages",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "The%20Final%20Fantasies",
            "The%20Espers",
            "The%20Rock%20Summoners"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"In%20the%20Kingdom%20Hearts%20series%2C%20which%20is%20not%20an%20optional%20boss%20you%20can%20fight%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Master%20Yen%20Sid",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Sephiroth",
            "Julius",
            "Kurt%20Zisa"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Science%3A%20Computers",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"According%20to%20DeMorgan%27s%20Theorem%2C%20the%20Boolean%20expression%20%28AB%29%27%20is%20equivalent%20to%3A",
         "correct_answer":"A%27%20%2B%20B%27",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "A%27B%20%2B%20B%27A",
            "A%27B%27",
            "AB%27%20%2B%20AB"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Science%3A%20Mathematics",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"Which%20of%20the%20following%20mathematicians%20made%20major%20contributions%20to%20game%20theory%3F",
         "correct_answer":"John%20Von%20Neumann",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Carl%20Friedrich%20Gauss",
            "Leonhard%20Euler",
            "Stefan%20Banach"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Sports",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"The%20Mazda%20787B%20won%20the%2024%20Hours%20of%20Le%20Mans%20in%20what%20year%3F",
         "correct_answer":"1991",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "1990",
            "2000",
            "1987"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Television",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"In%20the%20show%20%27Doctor%20Who%27%2C%20what%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20time-capsule%20model%20stolen%20by%20%27the%20Doctor%27%3F",
         "correct_answer":"TT%20Type%2040%2C%20Mark%203%20%28TARDIS%29",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "TT%20Type%201%2C%20Mark%203%20%28TARDIS%29",
            "TT%20Type%2040%2C%20Mark%205%20%28TARDIS%29",
            "TT%20Type%201%2C%20Mark%205%20%28TARDIS%29"
         ]
      },
      {
         "category":"Entertainment%3A%20Video%20Games",
         "type":"multiple",
         "difficulty":"hard",
         "question":"In%20the%202014%20Pokemon%20VGC%20Finals%2C%20which%20Pokemon%20was%20famous%20for%20bringing%20the%20winner%20to%20victory%3F",
         "correct_answer":"Pachirisu",
         "incorrect_answers":[
            "Garchomp",
            "Lapras",
            "Primal%20Groudon"
         ]
      }
   ]
}